<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>CodeCraft</title>
 <link href="http://www.codecraftuk.org/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://www.codecraftuk.org/"/>
 <updated>2014-02-05T21:25:59+00:00</updated>
 <id>http://www.codecraftuk.org</id>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Seven Languages in Seven Weeks, Part 2</title>
   <link href="http://www.codecraftuk.org/2014/02/seven-languages-part-2"/>
   <updated>2014-02-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.codecraftuk.org/2014/02/seven-languages-part-2</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For our second Seven Languages in Seven Weeks event, we'll be covering the remaining four languages: Scala, Erlang, Clojure and Haskell. We are encouraging programmers in and around Glasgow to read the excellent book, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.co.uk/dp/193435659X/&quot;&gt;Seven Languages in Seven Weeks&lt;/a&gt;, and follow-up by discussing what you learn with your peers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn't matter if you didn't make it to the first event (covering Ruby, Prolog and IO) or whether you have time to do all four chapters of the book: cover the languages you can with the time you have, and come and join the discussion regardless of your level of experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We encourage you to tackle the languages in any order, and bring along any examples you make along the way for further discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Details: Seven Languages in Seven Weeks: Scala, Erlang, Clojure and Haskell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Date - Thursday 20th March 2014&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Time - 7pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Location - &lt;a href=&quot;http://goo.gl/maps/N8vCM&quot;&gt;The Hope, 6/8 Waterloo Street, Glasgow, G2 6DA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Failures of Intro to TDD</title>
   <link href="http://www.codecraftuk.org/2014/02/failures-of-intro-tdd"/>
   <updated>2014-02-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.codecraftuk.org/2014/02/failures-of-intro-tdd</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As our first event in our new monthly slot (3rd Thursday of each month), we intend to get hands-on with an exploration of TDD. In his recent blog post, &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.testdouble.com/posts/2014-01-25-the-failures-of-intro-to-tdd.html&quot;&gt;The Failures of &quot;Intro to TDD&quot;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/searls&quot;&gt;Justin Searls&lt;/a&gt; makes the case that TDD is generally taught poorly, and provides a different way of exploring your design through tests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To see how well it works, we're going to be doing some hands-on practice (a kata or two) with classic TDD, London-School TDD and TDD reductionism (as described by Searls). So bring along a laptop if you have one handy, and we'll get coding. If you don't, don't worry, we should have enough between us to cover everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Details: The Failures of Intro to TDD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Date - Thursday 20th February 2014&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Time - 7pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Location - &lt;a href=&quot;http://goo.gl/maps/N8vCM&quot;&gt;The Hope, 6/8 Waterloo Street, Glasgow, G2 6DA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Seven Languages in Seven Weeks, Part 1</title>
   <link href="http://www.codecraftuk.org/2014/01/seven-languages-part-1"/>
   <updated>2014-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.codecraftuk.org/2014/01/seven-languages-part-1</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Looking for a new coding challenge for the New Year? Trying to pick up some new skills? Take the CodeCraft Seven Languages in Seven Weeks challenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For our first events, we are encouraging programmers in and around Glasgow to read the excellent book, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.co.uk/dp/193435659X/&quot;&gt;Seven Languages in Seven Weeks&lt;/a&gt;, and follow-up by discussing what you learn with your peers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our first event, on the &lt;strong&gt;4th February at 7pm&lt;/strong&gt;, will be dedicated to the first 3 languages in the book (Ruby, Prolog and IO), with the rest covered at the next event in March.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we hope you should have plenty of time to pick-up a copy of the book and study all three languages for February, we'd like to hear from you regardless of how much you manage to get through or your level of experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Details: Seven Languages in Seven Weeks: The First Three&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Date - Tuesday 4th February 2014&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Time - 7pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Location - &lt;a href=&quot;http://goo.gl/maps/N8vCM&quot;&gt;The Hope, 6/8 Waterloo Street, Glasgow, G2 6DA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
